{
    "id": "d9a241aa18d1462d80bb1fc502afeb80",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Lack ......................... money prevented her from going to university.",
            "description": "Lack + of",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "49330969dfdf48bdac5e964a0cf447eb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn't choose ............................... the two dresses.",
            "description": "Choose + between\r\nAmong is used to talk about more than two people or things.",
            "answers": [
                "among",
                "between",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6eb1296f954b47719ab66696c7014fb5"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is huge demand ............................. caps of this kind.",
            "description": "Demand + for",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "703b15bae25b47b994680b49bf16a4f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "After he became rich, his relationship ............................. his old friends changed a lot.",
            "description": "Relationship + with",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2b9fcb022312414ab0b777e15dff3e7c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The best solution ............................. many environmental problems is to use our resources wisely.",
            "description": "Solution + to",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a0827af1e5a1478489050052fb87fb49"
        },
        {
            "question": "As the item was out of stock, there was a delay ................................ delivery.",
            "description": "Delay + in",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "661e9bcdbcbe444a9f6e09d92754f06a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is an expert ....................................... child psychology.",
            "description": "Expert + on",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "89ecb6f4b8bb4d56959c5545aecf7d52"
        },
        {
            "question": "I often quarrel ............................... my friends.",
            "description": "Quarrel + with",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c01e5feb8bb44cf4b28968935083b6c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are the reason ............................... my problems.",
            "description": "Reason + for",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "91098fc032d9446ca127508d05d79acc"
        },
        {
            "question": "This law intends to protect animals .............................. cruelty.",
            "description": "Protect + from",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7f276e93919647a0b939c5f9afc5f40d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has no connection ............................... her family.",
            "description": "Connection + with",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "59b762b3662a49a6a7f37dcfad1b1e41"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are still millions of children who do not have access .................................. education.",
            "description": "Access + to",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3f6ee9cf052747aab2b9caa67cc5db77"
        }
    ]
}